<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!-- Copyright 2020 Neal Gompa <ngompa13@gmail.com> -->
<component type="desktop">
  <id>org.mageia.manafirewall.desktop</id>
  <metadata_license>CC-BY-SA-4.0</metadata_license>
  <project_license>GPL-2.0-or-later</project_license>
  <name>manafirewall</name>
  <name xml:lang="zh_CN">manafirewall</name>
  <name xml:lang="uk">manafirewall</name>
  <name xml:lang="sv">manafirewall</name>
  <name xml:lang="sr">manafirewall</name>
  <name xml:lang="sq">manafirewall</name>
  <name xml:lang="sl">manafirewall</name>
  <name xml:lang="pt_BR">manafirewall</name>
  <name xml:lang="nl">manafirewall</name>
  <name xml:lang="nb">manafirewall</name>
  <name xml:lang="ja">manafirewall</name>
  <name xml:lang="hi">manafirewall</name>
  <name xml:lang="fr">manafirewall</name>
  <name xml:lang="et">manafirewall</name>
  <name xml:lang="es">manafirewall</name>
  <name xml:lang="de">manafirewall</name>
  <name xml:lang="cs">manafirewall</name>
  <name xml:lang="ca">manafirewall</name>
  <name xml:lang="ast">manafirewall</name>
  <summary>A frontend to firewalld using libyui UI abstraction library</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="zh_CN">使用 libyui UI 抽象库的 firewalld 前端</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="uk">Оболонка до firewalld, створена з використання бібліотеки абстрагування від інтерфейсу користувача libyui</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sr">Сучеље за firewalld коришћењем libyui UI библиотеке за абстракцију</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sq">Një frontend të firewalld duke përdorur libyui UI biblioteka e abstraksioneve</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sl">Začelje za firewalld uporablja knjižnico libyui za upodabljanje uporabniškega vmesnika</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pt_BR">Uma interface para o firewalld usando a biblioteca de abstração UI libyui</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="nl">Een frontend voor firewalld die de libyui abstractiebibliotheek gebruikt voor de interface</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="nb">En frontend til firewalld ved hjelp av libyui UI-abstraksjonsbibliotek</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ja">libyui UI 抽象化ライブラリを用いた firewalld のフロントエンド</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="hi">उपयोक्ता अंतरफलक सारांश लाइब्रेरी libyui प्रयुक्त कर firewalld का फ्रंट-एंड</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="fr">Interface pour firewalld utilisant la bibliothèque d'abstraction graphique libyui.</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="et">firewalld kasutajaliides libyui kasutajaliidese abstraheerimise teegi põhjal</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="es">Interfaz para firewalld que utiliza la biblioteca libyui</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="de">Ein frontend für firewalld, das die Benutzerschnittstellen-Abstraktionsbibliothek libyui nutzt</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="cs">Grafické prostředí pro firewalld používající knihovnu libyui</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ca">Un frontal per a firewalld que usa la biblioteca d'abstracció de la IU libyui</summary>
  <description>
    <p>
     manafirewall is a firewalld frontend, inspired by firewall-config from firewalld project.
  </p>
    <p xml:lang="zh_CN">manafirewall 是一个 firewalld 前端，灵感来自 firewalld 项目的 firewall-config。</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">manafirewall — графічна оболонка до firewalld, ідею якої запозичено з firewall-config з проєкту firewalld.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sr">manafirewall је сучеље за firewalld, инспирисано firewall-config-опм за firewalld пројекат.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sq">manafirewall ështl njl firewalld frontend, frymëzuar nga firewall-config nga projekti firewalld.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sl">manafirewall je začelje za firewalld, z navdihom iz firewall-config iz projekta firewalld.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt_BR">manafirewall é uma interface do firewalld, inspirada pela firewall-config proveniente do projeto firewalld.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">manafirewall is een frontend voor firewalld, geïnspireerd op firewall-config van het firewalld-project.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nb">manafirewall er en firewallld frontend, inspirert av firewall-config fra firewalld-prosjektet.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ja">manafirewall は firewalld のフロントエンドで、firewalld プロジェクトの firewall-config から発想を得たものです。</p>
    <p xml:lang="hi">firewalld परियोजना के firewall-config से प्रेरित, firewalld का फ्रंट-एंड manafirewall है।</p>
    <p xml:lang="fr">manafirewall est une application pour firewalld, inspirée de firewall-config du projet firewalld.</p>
    <p xml:lang="et">manafirewall on firewalld kasutajaliides, mis on võtnud eeskuju firewalld projekti komponendist firewall-config.</p>
    <p xml:lang="es">manafirewall es una interfaz para firewalld inspirada por firewall-config del provecto firewalld</p>
    <p xml:lang="de">manafirewall ist ein Frontend für firewalld nach dem Vorbild des Programms firewall-config des firewalld-Projektes.</p>
    <p xml:lang="cs">manafirewall je grafické prostředí pro firewalld inspirovaný firewall-config z projektu firewalld</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca">manafirewall és un frontal per a firewalld, inspirat per firewall-config del projecte firewalld.</p>
    <p>
     manafirewall is written in Python 3 and uses libYui, the widget abstraction library written by SUSE,
     so that it can be run using Qt 5, GTK+ 3, or ncurses interfaces. It provides a frontend for the
     firewalld dbus firewall manager that can be used in any kind of system environment.
  </p>
    <p xml:lang="zh_CN">manafirewall 是用 Python 3 编写的，并使用 SUSE 编写的小部件抽象库 libYui，因此它可以使用 Qt 5、GTK+ 3 或 ncurses 接口运行。 它为 firewalld dbus 防火墙管理器提供了一个前端，可以在任何类型的系统环境中使用。 </p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">manafirewall написано мовою програмування Python 3, для чого використано libYui, бібліотеку абстрагування від віджетів, написану SUSE. Таким чином, програма може працювати з використанням інтерфейсів Qt 5, GTK+ 3 або ncurses. Вона забезпечує роботу оболонки програми для керування брандмауером за допомогою D-Bus, firewalld,, якою можна скористатися у будь-якому типі системного середовища.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sr">manafirewall је написан у Python 3 програмском језику коришћењем libYui, библиотеком за одвајање додатака коју је написао SUSE, тако да може да се покрене коришћењем Qt 5, GTK+ 3, или ncurses интерфејса. Омогућава сучеље за firewalld dbus менаџер заштитног зида које се може користити у било ком системском окружењу.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sq">manafirewall është shkruar në Python 3 dhe përdor libYui, biblioteka e abstraksionit të widgeteve e shkruar nga SUSE, në mënyrë që të mund të ekzekutohet duke përdorur Qt 5, GTK+ 3, ose ndërfaqen ncurses. Siguron një frontend për menaxherin e firewallld dbus firewalld që mund të përdoret në çdo lloj mjedisi të sistemit.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sl">manafirewall je napisa v jeziku Python 3 in uporablja libYui, gradnik za upodabljanje uporabniškega vmesnika, ki ga je napisal SUSE. Zato lahko teče v vmesnikih Qt 5, GTK+ 3 ali ncurses. Ponuja začelje za upravljalnik požarnega zidu firewalld dbus, ki ga je možno uporabiti v raznovrstnih sistemskih okoljih.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt_BR">manafirewall é escrito em Python 3 e usa libYui, a biblioteca de abstração de widgets escrita pela SUSE, para que possa ser executada usando as interfaces Qt 5, GTK+ 3, ou ncurses. Ele fornece uma interface para o gerenciador de firewall firewalld dbus que pode ser usado em qualquer tipo de ambiente do sistema.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">manafirewall is geschreven in Python 3 en gebruikt libYui, de widget-abstractiebibliotheek van SUSE, zodat het gebruikt kan worden met Qt 5, GTK+ 3 of ncurses interfaces. Het biedt een frontend voor de firewalld dbus firewall-beheerder die in elke systeemomgeving gebruikt kan worden.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nb">manafirewall er skrevet i Python 3 og bruker libYui, widgetabstraksjonsbiblioteket skrevet av SUSE, slik at det kan kjøres ved hjelp av grensesnittene Qt 5, GTK + 3 eller ncurses. Det gir en frontend for firewallld dbus brannmurbehandling som kan brukes i alle slags systemmiljøer.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ja">manafirewall は Python 3 で書かれ、Qt 5, GTK+ 3, ncurses インターフェースを用いて動作できるように、SUSE によって書かれた libYui ウィジェット抽象化ライブラリを使用しています。これはどのような種類のシステム環境でも使用可能な firewalld dbus ファイアウォール マネージャに対するフロントエンドを提供します。</p>
    <p xml:lang="hi">manafirewall पाइथन 3 में लिखित है व SUSE द्वारा रचित libYUI, विजेट सारांश लाइब्रेरी प्रयुक्त करने के कारणवश इसे क्यूटी 5, जीटीके+ 3 या ncurses अंतरफलकों में कार्यरत करना संभव है। यह firewalld dbus फ़ायरवॉल प्रबंधक हेतु फ्रंट-एंड प्रदान करता है जिसे किसी भी प्रकार के सिस्टम वातावरण में उपयोग कर सकते हैं।</p>
    <p xml:lang="fr">manafirewall est écrit en Python 3 et utilise libYui, une bibliothèque d'abstraction d'objet graphique écrite par SUSE, qui permet une interface en utilisant Qt 5, GTK+3 ou ncurses. Cette interface graphique au Gestionnaire de pare-feu firewalld via dbus peut être utilisée dans tout type d'environnement système.</p>
    <p xml:lang="et">manafirewall on kirjutatud Python 3 keeles ja see kasutab SUSE loodud vidinate abstraheerimise teeki libYui, mis tähendab, et see võib töötada Qt 5, GTK+ 3 või ncurses'i liidesega. See tekitab firewalld dbus'i tulemüürihalduri kasutajaliidese, mida on võimalik tarvitada kõikvõimalikes töökeskkondades.</p>
    <p xml:lang="es">manafirewall esta escrita en Python 3 y utiliza libYui, la biblioteca de abstracción de widget escrita por SUSE, con la que se pueden crear interfaces Qt 5, GTK+ 3, o ncurses. Proporciona una interfaz para el gestor de cortafuegos firewalld mediante dbus, puede ser utilizada en cualquier tipo de entorno de sistemas.</p>
    <p xml:lang="de">manafirewall ist in Python 3 programmiert und nutzt libYui, eine Widget-Abstraktionsbibliothek von SUSE. Daher läuft es mit einer Qt5-, GTK+ 3- oder ncurses-Bedienoberfläche. Es bietet ein Frontend für firewalld, den dbus-Firewall-Manager, und kann in jeder Art von Systemumgebung eingesetzt werden.</p>
    <p xml:lang="cs">manafirewall je napsán v Pythonu 3 a používá libYui, knihovnu abstrakce widgetů napsanou SUSE, takže ji lze spustit pomocí Qt 5, GTK + 3 nebo ncurses. Poskytuje rozhraní pro firewalld dbus, které lze použít v jakémkoli prostředí systému.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca">manafirewall està escrit amb Python 3 i usa libYui, la biblioteca d'abstracció d'estris escrita per SUSE, de manera que es pugui executar usant les interfícies Qt 5, GTK+ 3 o ncurses. Proporciona una interfície gràfica per al gestor del tallafoc dbus de firewalld que es pot usar en qualsevol tipus d'entorn de sistema.</p>
  </description>
  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default" width="1706" height="862">
       https://raw.githubusercontent.com/manatools/manafirewall/master/screenshots/manafirewall-Runtime_zone_services-qt.png
   </screenshot>
  </screenshots>
  <url type="homepage">https://github.com/manatools/manafirewall</url>
  <update_contact>ngompa_at_mageia.org</update_contact>
</component>
